(Raj:)I'd throw it at
your head right now.
(Howard:)I'll keep rockin'.
You don't do that.
(Raj:)Okay. I posted it.
(Howard:)So, who is this guy?
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
Uh, his name is Trent Monaco.
(Howard:)Cool name.
Yeah.
(Raj:)He's 24. He's a deejay.
(Raj:)He brews his own beer.
He's got
(Raj:)awesome tattoos. Dude, he's
got a hot girlfriend, too.
(Howard:)Damn. I don't know if he's
our biggest fan or I'm his.
(phone chimes)
(Howard:)Hey, Trent just liked
our comment.
He is so cool!
(Raj:)No hard feelings,
(Raj:)but I'm throwing my
hypothetical bra at him.
(tune playing on keyboard
in distance)
(tune repeating, slower)
(Penny:)Oh, my God, he won't stop.
(Leonard:)How does he keep coming up
with new ways to be annoying?